[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[In my prime]
[Episode 12]
[Two months later]
Time to get off the bus.
Qi Zhi!
Si!
Is Qi Zhi still our son?
He wouldn't listen
to a word I say.
My goodness.
I can't believe he went
t-to meet Cao Si behind my back again.
He said they just ran into
each other, didn't he?
"Ran into each other"?
Only you would believe that lie of his.
For what reason would they
come back at the exact same time?
Too coincidental to be true, wasn't it?
Our son truly cares
a lot about Cao Si.
What do you mean?
The grudges between our families aside,
we did watch
Cao Si
grow up.
We know her well.
What now?
You want to be in-laws
with Cao Dongfang?
Who?
You.
Who said that?
I've never had that thought.
Regardless of what kind
of person Cao Dongfang is,
Cao Si is quite
a decent young woman
with great character.
Haven't you
always liked her too?
That's another matter, really.
Whether our son can make the national team
depends on his efforts
in this year and the next.
Whether it's Cao Si or anyone else,
if they hold my son back
from the provincial or national team,
I will... I will fight them till I die!
Under no circumstances
will I agree to
let them be a couple!
Mom fights
as fiercely as ever.
You're smart.
Come up with a solution for me.
Do you remember
how we made Grandma go back home
that time she visited?
When Grandma was here, she took you
to collect cardboard every day,
causing your grades to drop.
Then your teacher came over
and talked to her.
Grandma felt sorry
for distracting you from your studies.
Exactly.
Then let's say
keeping you
from dating Cao Si compromises
your performance at the sports school.
How do you think Mom will react?
Right.
We can use that tactic again
and make Mom give in.
Let's go.
I didn't finish the game!
An important matter awaits us.
Hurry!
What do you two want with me?
I was in a crucial round!
Just go! Go!
Ouch, it hurts!
Let go of me.
Qi Zhi's performance has been
utterly unsatisfactory
during these two months of training.
The coaching team is very disappointed
with his performance.
What are you laughing at?
What's funny about this?
This won't do.
You'll definitely give a tell.
I told you he couldn't handle this.
He was terrible at acting as a cat
in the stage play last time.
He even had the nerve
to go on stage.
I was completely immersed in
the role.
Wait, you two asked me for help,
and now you're criticizing me?
Speaking of being pretentious,
I've thought of someone.
Hello, Mrs. Qi.
I'm Qi Zhi's assistant coach.
Qi Zhi's performance has been
utterly unsatisfactory
during these two months of training.
Alright, you're on it.
It takes a fortune to have me
make an appearance.
Two sets of hangers.
Hangers.
Soap.
Hello?
Hello.
This is Qi Zhi's assistant coach.
Qi Zhi's assistant coach?
Hello, hello.
The coaching team is very disappointed
with Zhi's performance.
At this rate,
let alone the national team,
I'm afraid he won't even make it
to the provincial games.
Wait, Coach.
Coach, please calm down.
P-Please don't be mad.
Zhi is probably
a bit emotionally unstable
since he is going through puberty.
When your child is upset,
as his parents,
you shouldn't go firmly against him.
At the very least,
before he could make the provincial team,
your priority
should be soothing his emotions.
Well, then, Coach,
how do we do that?
How do you do that?
You need me to teach you how?
Just buy him
whatever he wants to eat.
Let him do
what he wants to do.
The biggest taboo for parents
is overreaching and being too controlling.
When you do that...
Anyway,
I hope he will be in better shape
and show some spirit
as he attends the next training camp.
Okay. Coach, I...
Alright.
The show is over.
Now you can have a month's worth
of mock exams
What did the coach say?
He told us not
to be too controlling,
and that we should soothe Zhi's emotions.
We should let him eat and do
whatever he wants.
The provincial games are approaching.
It's no good for our son
to keep being so down.
It would definitely irritate the coach.
What should we do then?
I've tried talking
some sense into Zhi,
but he just wouldn't listen.
The coach was right.
At the current stage,
we surely have to
prioritize Qi Zhi's future.
How about...
we tell our son this:
as long as he makes it
to the provincial team,
we may allow him and Cao Si to get
together.
No way!
Your spit flew right into my eye.
Son,
as long as you get admitted
to the provincial team,
we may make a concession
on you dating Cao Si.
Is that an approval, Mom?
If you make the provincial team,
everything will be negotiable.
Son, rest assured.
Your mom always
keeps her word.
We are all witnesses to that.
But I have one condition.
Say it, Mom.
Before you make the team,
you must focus on training
and refrain from seeing Cao Si.
Mom, I promise
I will focus on training.
I'll make
you, Cao Si,
and the coach proud.
I'll make Dad and my sister
proud too.
The coach said
though we're on break,
strength training must go on.
I'm going out for extra training!
You...
Careful.
He didn't even finish lunch.
My mom said
she'd allow Zhi to date Cao Si
once he made it to the provincial team.
But before that, the two of them
must not meet up.
How come it gives me a feeling
that Mrs. Huo is just stalling?
It doesn't matter.
What matters
is that my mom's words
basically
gave Zhi a free pass.
My dad and I both heard it.
We are witnesses to her words.
My mom can't go back on that.
Zhi also said
that he'd like to see Cao Si one more time
before leaving for training.
He asked us
to cover for him.
Okay.
These are for you.
Si,
I'm sorry
to upset you these past two months.
My coach
removed the phone from my dorm.
So, I...
I know.
Qi Shi already
had Cao Xin pass the message to me.
Well then...
will you still
stick with me?
My family won't let me.
Si,
I don't care if my mom and others agree
to let us be together.
As long as our hearts are as one,
nothing can stop us.
Someone once said
that love is like a long-distance race.
To sprint for the gold medal and win,
it's certainly
important to have
all the favorable factors,
but what matters more
is persistence.
It's persistence.
Persistence...
As an athlete,
I know the meaning of persistence
better than anyone does.
I...
What is this?
Si.
How dare you.
You even made a cheat sheet for this.
No, it's not like that.
Indeed,
I asked Qi Shi to write this for me.
But I was lying to you.
This is exactly what I meant to say.
You done covering for Zhi?
Your mom is a real pain in the neck.
She's buying beans for me
at the market right now.
The peeling will take her a while.
Okay.
Look.
Love in real life is no less
dramatic than in TV dramas.
All you know
is TV dramas.
I'm not like that, alright?
But I do think
you said it right.
One must be persistent,
try to do they want to do,
and bravely love
whoever they want to love.
Then all obstacles
will become insignificant.
Si,
my mom has made her stance clear.
As long as I win the championship
at the provincial games
and make the provincial team,
I'll have a final showdown
with them, whether they
approve of us being together or not.
I,
Qi Zhi,
will marry no one but Cao Si!
Keep it down.
What are you doing?
Don't block my view.
I didn't see it!
Easy on it.
You've had three bowls of rice.
Shall I get you one more?
Slow down.
Fried mushrooms for you.
Look at this.
All empty.
I'll get him some steamed buns.
This is enough for me, Dad.
What's with him?
As I told you,
when dealing with children,
parents should use the right methods.
See?
The solution we came up with previously
is working quite well now, isn't it?
Look at you, so cocky.
Just eat your food.
I'm leaving.
Mom, Dad, I am
leaving for training.
Have you finished lunch?
Yes.
I-Is there money on you?
I-I'll buy the ticket for you.
No, I'm good. I've got some money left.
How about I walk you to the station?
No need, Dad. I'll run there.
Bye!
Be careful on the way.
What a kid.
Do you remember
what I told you two to do?
Boss,
rest assured.
We've got this.
Si.
I like you.
I've liked you since we were kids.
I like you from the bottom of my heart.
Let's get it settled today.
If you agree to be my girlfriend,
just nod.
He's saying he likes her?
Yeah.
What a grand gesture.
I'm sorry.
So romantic.
I've given my heart to someone.
He got rejected.
And it's not you.
Impossible.
Are you being shy or what?
Have you never liked me?
She nodded!
No, never.
Congrats, Boss.
You're no longer single.
Boss,
how do you feel now?
Are you thrilled?
Are you excited?
Stop filming.
-Boss.
-Boss!
My apologies.
I'm terribly sorry.
Sorry.
What happened?
Why the long face?
Does someone owe you money?
Hault!
Why are you pulling a long face?
Got into trouble again?
Stop shaking your head. Say something.
Are you short on money again?
Dad,
Si rejected me.
She said she has a boyfriend now.
Please.
There are so many nice girls out there.
Why must you fall for
Cao Dongfang's daughter?
Dad,
she already stole my heart!
You...
Wait...
♪ Moonlight rests upon the window sill ♪
♪ While shadows linger close by ♪
♪ I've slowly learn to ♪
♪ Confess my loneliness to myself ♪
♪ While still a child ♪
♪ No one wants to master joy in sorrow ♪
♪ But some people are born unlucky ♪
♪ And never favored by heaven ♪
♪ The gale and the heavy rain ♪
♪ The faded traces at the alley entrance ♪
My mom has made her stance clear.
As long as I win the championship
at the provincial games
♪ Why does this world ♪
and make the provincial team,
♪ Have to slander ♪
I'll have
a final showdown with them,
whether they approve of
us being together or not.
♪ What I believe again ♪
I,
Qi Zhi,
will marry no one but Cao Si!
♪ Still, I will love; still, I may lose ♪
♪ Still, I will not look back ♪
♪ Looking foolish in the light ♪
♪ I will choose to be the exception ♪
♪ No matter how slight the chance ♪
♪ I will reach for it ♪
♪ Because this life of mine ♪
♪ Is meant for something brighter ♪
Mom, Dad,
I clocked 10.24 seconds today.
Do you know what
that number means?
This year's champion of
the provincial games
ran 10.23 seconds.
And I did 10.24 seconds.
That's not much of a difference.
Our son's only 0.01 seconds slower.
Son, worker a bit harder and you will
make the provincial team, right?
Son,
you've got this.
Do try harder.
Alright.
I'm hanging up and leaving
for training.
Bye.
Okay. Sure.
Bye then.
If our son performs well,
maybe in a few years,
he'll take the lead in the Olympics
and win a championship.
Then I can tell everyone
that I am
the father of an Olympic champion.
Exactly.
Well,
can you, the mother
of a future Olympic champion,
give me 800 yuan?
What for?
I plan to sign up
for a Math Olympiad training class.
My homeroom teacher said
since I am good at math,
I could probably
win a prize in the Math Olympiad.
Zhi's expenses at the sports school
are covered by the school.
Why does it cost so much
to support you through school?
It's a good thing
that our child is motivated.
Besides,
that's a recommendation by her teacher.
Exactly because of her good grades
and potential,
she's qualified for this training class.
Right?
Right.
Stop pretending to be generous.
You...
Can we afford that much?
How much did you make today?
How much?
Two hundred?
Only twenty.
How dare you act the hero
with that little money?
Off you go. Wash the dishes!
And you!
You're taking
the college entrance exam next year.
What's the point
of attending extra training?
Go! Study all you want.
Just teach yourself.
She should stay down-to-earth
and focus on the exam.
Right?
Cut out that nonsense—
it's expansive and distracting.
I heard everything just now.
I happened to receive my salary today.
I'm Qi Shi's father.
My daughter is my responsibility.
Don't you butt in.
She wants to attend a training class,
doesn't she?
Dad, what are you doing?
There is...
320.5 yuan.
I saved it up in secret.
Take it.
Go for that training class.
I'll pay the rest
of the fee later.
No need.
Keep the money for yourself.
Why?
Are you not attending the training class?
Won't you participate
in the Math Olympiad?
I will.
I'll attend the training class too.
But I'd like to
make it happen with my own efforts.
With your own efforts?
H-How do you do that?
Dad.
Has your business
been lacking sparks lately?
What do you mean?
You want to set my stall on fire?
They're fighting.
Would I harm you?
You've used it.
I'll charge you 3 yuan,
since you're a friend.
Medicated oil for sale!
Buy medicated oil,
get free answer sheets.
Buy one bottle, get one sheet free.
Buy two bottles, get three sheets free.
The more you buy, the more you get!
Don't miss out on the sale.
Buy it now, or never!
You want medicated oil?
Qi Shi. Qi Shi!
I don't need answer sheets,
just a bottle of medicated oil.
Okay.
Qi Shi.
I'll take 2 bottles of medicated oil.
Two bottles, right?
Here you are.
I'll take 5 bottles.
Five?
W-Where's the pay?
You plan to drink it?
I'll take 3 bottles.
I'll take 4.
Okay.
You're violating school rules.
Four bottles, right?
I'll take 5 bottles.
I can't give you that many now.
Take two for the time being.
Pass this along
for me.
And we want answer sheets.
How many for you?
He should get three. You...
I won't take any sheets.
Give me a 20% discount instead.
I advise you to buy a second bottle.
Then you'll receive 3 answer sheets
for free.
Two are for this time.
Save the third one
for the next exam. I'll tutor you.
Have you paid yet?
Here you are.
They're sold out.
Have you paid yet?
Good business today, huh?
Yeah.
School's out?
Yes.
Counting money, Dad?
Good sales today, huh?
Just back from school?
I'm telling you,
Sweetie,
I truly hit the jackpot today.
Do you know how much stuff
I sold today?
How much?
Come sit down. Let me tell you.
Today, altogether,
I sold
eight bars of soap,
six towels,
five bottles of floral water,
and two packs of mosquito coils.
What do you think? Awesome, right?
How about you?
How much stuff did you sell today?
Sweetie,
you're indeed smart,
but you might not be
cut out for business.
Listen,
there's a lot to learn
when it comes to doing business.
You really need to study hard.
Take me as an example.
I earned so much money in just one day.
Your mom definitely
won't yell at me when I get home.
Of course she won't.
Look.
I sold each
and every item.
All of them?
Look.
One hundred and eight.
As per our agreement,
I take a third of it,
and you keep the rest.
Sure. Go ahead.
You sold all the items.
Here you are.
Okay.
I only sold a few bottles
of medicated oil in over half a month.
Never did I imagine you could
sell them out in one day.
Truly impressive.
But the profit margin is just too low.
At this rate,
when will I save
enough for the fee of the training class?
We're just running a tiny stall.
What can we sell, if not these?
In my opinion,
we should
supply on demand
and seek opportunities from customers.
Supply on demand?
Sir,
I'll take a fan.
Coming right up.
Look at mine.
Two yuan.
Let me see.
So handsome.
Right?
Just made another two yuan.
Sweetie,
I've even put the money
your mom gave me for inventory
into this.
Do you think these photos
will really sell?
The people on them
don't seem as handsome as me
in my youth.
Dad,
you know little about this.
They are all super stars
and very popular.
Really?
Their photos will surely sell
better
than medicated oil.
We'll split the profits
as we agreed.
You'll definitely get your share.
Absolutely.
We're business partners now, after all.
But business is business.
Don't neglect your studies.
Once you save enough for the fee,
stop doing this.
Don't worry,
I know what I'm doing.
I'm leaving then.
Off you go.
Si.
I swear,
I'm truly in love with you.
Zhou Xuanyu,
I've told you
I have a boyfriend now.
I know.
But you two aren't married.
It's not illegal for me to pursue you.
Do you think this is fun?
I just can't help it.
My heart aches when a day passes
without seeing you.
If necessary, just
treat me as some stranger.
Stop wasting
your time on me.
No.
How is it a waste of time
when I am with someone I like?
You have the right to reject me.
I have the right to pursue you.
Besides,
who knows what the future holds?
If you break up with Zhi one day,
I'll stand a chance with you, won't I?
Zhou Xuanyu,
don't you have shame?
She's already with someone,
yet you're still clinging to her.
You want to embarrass your dad or what?
What does this have to do with you?
What does this have to do with me?
Si is my future sister-in-law.
I was wondering why Qi Zhi
would interfere that day.
So he's the man you're with?
How is he better than me?
You chose him?
He's so silly.
Who are you calling silly?
My brother is better than you
in every way.
You are nowhere
near as good as him.
I'm warning you,
stay away from Si from now on.
Or I will spare you no mercy.
Why are you staring?
Didn't you learn a lesson
when I beat you up
in childhood?
Still staring, huh?
Si,
if he pesters you again,
just let me know.
I'll fix him for you.
I know.
You're truly something, just like
when you were little.
Of course.
You're my future sister-in-law.
When Zhi is away,
I must protect you in his stead.
What's in your backpack?
It seems heavy.
Look.
I didn't lie to you, did I?
I have everything you want.
Limited editions.
Ten yuan for each.
These look pretty nice.
Senior,
a picture of Hua Ze Lei for me.
Here's the pay.
And I want a photo of Avril Lavigne.
This one is handsome.
Senior, I'll take this one.
So cute.
T-This one is good too.
Look.
He look a bit like Cao Xin, right?
One photo.
Cao Xin? Let me see.
The two of them do look alike.
I've seen Cao Xin play basketball.
I was totally impressed
by his flawless side profile
from every angle.
He's so cute.
Let me see.
-Let me see.
-Me too.
Let me see.
Girls, Cao Xin is not only
good at basketball,
but also at studying.
I heard he made it to the top
three of the grade again.
-Really? Impressive.
-He's good.
He's truly handsome.
Handsome and smart.
Cute and tall.
He is pretty good.
I think he's even cuter than Hua Ze Lei.
Do you girls want
photos of Cao Xin?
-Cao Xin?
Unreleased photos.
Wonderful moments
you can't see at school.
-I want those!
-So do I!
-Senior.
-I want those.
-I do too.
Qi Shi ranks first
in the grade every year,
and she has strong business acumen.
A talent like her
will surely stand out
and become a business elite
even without going
to a top university.
Guys, how does she get first place
when she's always distracted?
You want to know?
There's no such thing as free lunch
in the world.
In exchange for my study secrets,
lend me your camera for two days.
What do you need my camera for?
It doesn't concern you.
Just tell me if you'll say yes or no.
No.
Suit yourself.
Forget about the secrets then.
How stingy.
Why was the flash on?
Why take photos of me in secret?
I'm not.
I'm just testing your camera.
Still in denial.
I saw it with my own eyes.
How could you deny it?
You don't have a crush on me,
do you?
You're overthinking it.
Who would have a crush on you?
I was just...
Graduation is approaching, isn't it?
I just wanted to take some photos
as a souvenir.
You could've just told me so.
Why so sneaky?
I would've allowed it.
Really?
What are you doing?
No, wait...
You have no manners at all.
How is he so handsome?
Yours is not bad, actually.
He looks so cute in this one.
Yeah, he looks so good when he smiles.
So handsome!
Cao!
He's so cute!
Not bad.
Your fan club even
dug up unreleased photos of you.
He's so handsome.
So handsome.
Qi Shi!
What have you done?
Why so mad?
You allowed
me to take photos of you, didn't you?
How was I supposed to know
you meant to...
Did you really think
I wanted to keep photos or you?
How's that possible?
Class monitor.
The fee for the Math Olympiad
training class.
Count it.
You went through all this trouble
just to earn the fee?
What else reason could there be?
I always keep my word.
My study secrets
and all the key knowledge points
are in here.
It covers everything, right?
I stayed up all night writing this.
Look at my hand.
It's practically disabled.
Aren't you afraid of ranking
below me in the next monthly exam?
No, not at all.
If you do outperform me,
then buy me breakfast for a month.
I have to buy breakfast
for a month if I win?
You're quite the businesswoman.
If you defeat me because you have read
my study secrets,
shouldn't you treat me to breakfast?
Then if you win,
you'll have to buy me breakfast.
No way.
You didn't write me any study secrets.
Have you ever heard of repaying kindness?
Qi Shi!
Time to eat!
Coming.
Zongzi?
Come on.
They're hot.
Eat zongzi at the Dragon Boat Festival...
After Zhi eats zongzi
at the Dragon Boat Festival,
he'll dominate the track.
After you eat zongzi
at the Dragon Boat Festival,
you'll outsmart prodigies.
This one has cured meat.
L-Leave this for Zhi.
T-That ingredient's bad for you.
You should have one with red dates.
This one. This green one
contains red dates.
I want sugar then.
No problem.
Aunt Lingzhi spent
the entire morning making these.
You're back.
It's so hot today.
So hot...
Look, so much sweat on your back.
Here.
Let me wipe your face.
Okay.
I can do it myself.
Why is it so hot today?
Honey.
Count this.
Go ahead.
This...
W-Why has your business been so good
these past few months?
Honey,
I'm not bragging,
but I am a bit talented
in doing
business.
Cows eat grass. Bears eat meat.
As long as we cater to
the customers' demands,
there's no worry about raking in profit.
Right, Sweetie?
Exactly.
With his experience
as a street vendor for 10 years,
my dad has finally summarized
such a profound theory.
What a real business prodigy.
Well, it...
Business prodigy, my foot.
He was just in luck.
Listen,
seriously,
t-the building of the nearby market
is almost finished.
Let's go check it out
someday
and pick a good spot.
Alright?
We should quickly
secure a place.
Okay.
This one has cured meat.
Got it.
Now, our family
finally has some property.
I've come up with a name for our shop.
It'll be "Qi's Grocery Store."
What do you think?
Sounds great, doesn't it?
It seems like
a century-old shop, right?
Exactly.
Right?
A century-old shop?
I'm telling you,
our kids won't suffer
like you do.
But at least now
we have a store, right?
We won't have to be exposed
to the sun and rain anymore.
I have good news too.
I won first prize
in the national Math Olympiad finals.
My teacher said
this could add 15 points
to my college entrance exam result.
Fifteen points?
My goodness.
Our daughter's amazing.
You've left
all the others miles behind!
See, I told you so.
What's the point of a training class?
You did great
on your own, didn't you?
Seriously.
Come on!
A chicken drumstick as a reward for you.
Then...
I want one too.
You want one too?
Here's a big one for you,
since you brought back so much money.
Honey,
could you give me
a little more allowance?
Are you craving alcohol again?
Where is that from?
The allowance
you give me every month
adds up to less than 100 yuan.
How is that enough?
One hundred is not enough?
You eat and drink at home
with no worries about the social expenses.
How are you not satisfied?
Tell me
w-where do you spend money.
What for?
Never mind.
I know
you must be craving alcohol.
Just drop the act!
It's Zhi?
Son,
how have you been lately? Good?
Your dad, your sister and I are
doing great.
Your sister got wonderful grades.
Let me tell you,
your dad's business
has been picking up lately.
I'll give you 200 yuan for allowance.
I'm doing great too.
Thanks, Mom.
Mom, I've got news for you too.
I broke
my personal best record
again this month.
My coach has recommended me
to the provincial team.
That's great, Son.
Keep up the good work.
Win a few
more awards.
After you make the provincial team,
bring a national championship
home.
The Qi family
is counting on you to bring honor back!
That's right, Zhi.
Here, we'd like to
toast to you in advance,
our future
national champion.
Sure,
second prize winner of the Math Olympiad.
Well done, Xin.
You did a great job.
But don't get cocky.
The college entrance exam is coming up.
You must devote yourself
to reviewing knowledge during these days.
Aim for Tsinghua and Peking University.
Here you are,
Grandpa.
Okay.
Dad,
I'd like to discuss something with you.
When it's time to apply
for a major, I want to choose
mechanical engineering.
I heard a lot of people have picked
this major lately.
This way, finding a job after graduation
will be easier.
Sounds great.
Xin has always enjoyed fiddling
with gadgets since he was little.
I remember when he was
about seven or eight,
he once
took my transistor radio apart.
Oh my goodness.
It was the precious radio
that I couldn't live without!
He scattered the parts all over the table.
I got so mad.
But in the blink of an eye,
he put it back together.
It happened, right?
Yeah.
He has also made me
an electric massager.
It works really well.
Several colleagues of mine asked
where I bought it.
Xin,
go for it.
I think that engineering thingy
you mentioned is a suitable major
for you.